<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Salman&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://isalman.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Salman&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 01:59:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isalman.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I Think Crypto Is Halaal? Some myths about Cryptocurrencies</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/why-i-think-crypto-is-halaal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 01:59:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/why-i-think-crypto-is-halaal/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency works on blockchain and blockchain is a decentralized system that is not governed by a country or an organization. Its circulation is limited (some exceptions) and its value may increase decrease and these tokens are mined similarly it possesses characteristics just like gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initialize GitHub Like Blog</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/init/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 19:09:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/init/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hello World, this is my attempt to implement github like blog using static site generator with markdown support.
Lets see were we will go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day When Facebook Stored User Passwords in Plain-Text Without Encryption – Facebook Apologized 😂</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/the-day-when-facebook-stored-password-as-plain-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 20:01:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/the-day-when-facebook-stored-password-as-plain-text/</guid>
      <description>Being a Tech Giant is not everything. Facebook holds majority of market in Social Media Networking Platform out there. Recently 3 days before on April 2nd 2019 Google abandoned it’s Social Media Platform ‘Google +’. Well if they would have abandoned it on 1st April it would have been April Fool’s day for the creators of Google Plus.
Well coming back to Facebook , I am sci-fan &amp;amp; believe “With Great Power Comes Greater Responsibility” but having so much controversies within Facebook on security aspect – Well they come with nothing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want To Start Your Programming Career? Don’t Know Where To Start? This 3-Min Article Might Help You</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/start-your-programming-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:43:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/start-your-programming-career/</guid>
      <description>You wanna start you programming career and don’t know where to start it happens all the time with everyone. So without confusing you more, I’ll tell you some of the basics where to start and which programming language to go for.
For the starters:
The basic trend is to go for “C” Language as it’s said that its the mother of all of the languages!
But let me pause you for a second, choosing a programming language as a fresher is really important because if you choose wrong the consequences are:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
