<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Salman&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://isalman.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Salman&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 22:07:36 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isalman.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Find Anything on Internet With Google Dorking - Google Dorking 101</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/google-dorking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 22:07:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/google-dorking/</guid>
      <description>We all use Google or other search engine for our daily queries and other questions over internet. And we almost get our desired results back from Google.
But there might be some issues when you want to search something but you cannot get the results because that search topic is either new or does not have many public results. This problem is mostly faced by researchers where the information for the particular neeche is very limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Think Crypto Is Halaal? Some myths about Cryptocurrencies</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/why-i-think-crypto-is-halaal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 01:59:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/why-i-think-crypto-is-halaal/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency works on blockchain and blockchain is a decentralized system that is not governed by a country or an organization. Its circulation is limited (some exceptions) and its value may increase decrease and these tokens are mined similarly it possesses characteristics just like gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initialize GitHub Like Blog</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/init/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 19:09:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/init/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hello World, this is my attempt to implement github like blog using static site generator with markdown support.
Lets see were we will go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All You Need to Know About New Hermes Javascript Engine How to Migrate</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/all-you-need-to-know-about-new-hermes-javascript-engine-how-to-migrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 20:04:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/all-you-need-to-know-about-new-hermes-javascript-engine-how-to-migrate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SO FACEBOOK JUST OPEN SOURCE ANOTHER JAVASCRIPT ENGINE NAMED AS HERMES.&lt;br&gt;
IT IS A JAVASCRIPT ENGINE SPECIFICALLY TAILORED FOR RUNNING WITH MOBILE APPLICATIONS THAT IS PRIMARILY WITH REACT NATIVE ON ANDROID BECAUSE ON IOS YOU ARE FORCED TO USE V8.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Full Stack Developer Only With This Programming Language</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/become-full-stack-developer-only-with-this-programming-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 20:12:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/become-full-stack-developer-only-with-this-programming-language/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With lots of programming language out  there  everyone here is getting confused about what to follow and what not to. All programming languages having their own limitations and their own pros and cons. At the beginning of this article,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Day When Facebook Stored User Passwords in Plain-Text Without Encryption – Facebook Apologized 😂</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/the-day-when-facebook-stored-password-as-plain-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 20:01:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/the-day-when-facebook-stored-password-as-plain-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Being a Tech Giant is not everything. Facebook holds majority of market in Social Media Networking Platform out there. Recently 3 days before on April 2nd 2019 Google abandoned it’s Social Media Platform ‘Google +’.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn React Js in 6 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/learn-react-js-in-6-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 20:25:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/learn-react-js-in-6-minutes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-quick-introduction-to-the-popular-javascript-library&#34;&gt;A quick introduction to the popular JavaScript library.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://web.archive.org/web/20200814103403/https://scrimba.com/g/glearnreact?ref=salmanually.com&#34;&gt;Just In case you want deep drive in react Click here to get to the free course on react.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now let’s get started!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-setup&#34;&gt;The setup&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When getting started with React, you should use the simplest setup possible: an HTML file which imports the  &lt;code&gt;React&lt;/code&gt;  and the  &lt;code&gt;ReactDOM&lt;/code&gt;  libraries using script tags, like this:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want To Start Your Programming Career? Don’t Know Where To Start? This 3-Min Article Might Help You</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/start-your-programming-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:43:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/start-your-programming-career/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You wanna start you programming career and don’t know where to start it happens all the time with everyone. So without confusing you more, I’ll tell you some of the basics where to start and which programming language to go for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Ajax in 5 Mins</title>
      <link>https://isalman.dev/post/learn-ajax-in-5-mins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 20:16:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isalman.dev/post/learn-ajax-in-5-mins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yes you heard it right! You can learn AJAX in 5 mins provided you have little concepts of javaScript and jQuery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The method I am sharing with you right now will probably boot your AJAX skills.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
